And we'll start in the minute or so.
All right, forget the start.
So let's go from the top
here. Um, last week we had
a short meeting this.
That play appreciation weekend.
Most of us were kind of busy,
but hoping to get some additional updates
this week. We'll start with the App
assessments Apple onboarding plan. So
let's take the app onboarding plan was
approved. And we
had one application remaining. I believe
that is still the case. So
tomorrow I saw an e-mail from
legal. Looks like they made their
updates. So they're looking for business
owner approval. We actually just had
a meeting earlier this morning to
review it. The business owner,
so it's progressing, but
yeah, still outstanding.
Sounds good. And
I guess on a similar topic
to this, we also have two
applications that are currently.
In pilot going to production within the
next couple of weeks to enable MFA
and enter ID. One of them is
completed path and the other one is
PAT is ongoing this week and we
have tentative dates for June 25th or
one of the applications and. The
second one is TBD, so we will
have a couple of applications onboarded
with MFA enabled in the coming weeks.
Only one OK Next up
is the entry ID application
onboarding process. So we have
here 2 parts. So the
SSO, application registration,
self-service capabilities we can start
with that.
Trust from ID wants to
chime in here. Yep, I.
We were able to.
Ship so some of our contractors over from
another program that isn't starting until
the end of July to work on this.
I think you might have gotten an update
prior, Andrew. So I actually level set
with them yesterday and also an hour this
morning and I've gotten them going, Paul.
Umm, they're, they're going to reach back
out to you as well, I think, based on
some of the conversation we had this
morning. Primary on that
is Michael Daddy, but three of them are
kind of tag teaming on this for knowledge
transfer, so.
I gave them a bunch of technical
background on the pipeline development
pieces and then directed them to you for
some of the specific app registration
questions that they had related to some
of the functionality. And I've asked them
to focus on the core uplifts that were
remaining first before getting into the
MLB stuff. Yeah, I think
those were, I think those were pretty
much done and I was actually able to
figure out, yeah, that's why I wanted to
talk to you from voting for sure. Yeah. I
wasn't sure what brand had completed
versus not completed. So, yeah, I think
the the ones for the delivery team to
deliver stuff are are I think they're
done. I think Keisha's been done.
But I think there's like button that up
and then there's like 4 tickets that were
not started that were clearly for the
core module, right? Like skin
provisioning and a few others. Ohh well.
OK. I guess I view those as
kind of bonus goals because it is
pretty rare. So it's like, but yeah,
fair if we wanted to do those
first, but I wasn't clear, right? Like
customize identifier, Uri, custom
security attribute, default behaviors.
I should have clarified which ones were
everyday needs and which ones are niche
edge cases. They're the ones that remain
are edge cases so it doesn't make sense
to have them. But they're not like ohh
yeah some of them might be not worth the
squeeze in some cases if if it's if
Terraform doesn't like it or something.
Believe me for you, but I'll also be in
around the salon. So like we need to
connect and Paul with these guys and just
make sure that we understand what it is.
So if if they're clear to start working
on the MLB stuff versus and the other
stuff is just going by undertaking
validation from Keyshawn, then we should
track that and understand if there's
updates. That we need to make to the
against the validation that's happening.
Or anything else, right. Or if we can
just get right into the self-service
stuff, which would be like the other
thing with the to the to the Michael and
team. Do they know how to promote things
out of anger? Because that's where it is
right now. Not yet, but they're working
with Dave Lloyd, who absolutely does.
Yeah, I know Dave does. I didn't know
whether I'd go to David Warren or
somebody to. That to to start elevating
out of death. Yeah, we're elevating out
of engine, which is so it's pretty well
documented too. And they've they've been
they've gone to KD from Dave Lloyd and
and they can they're going to come to me
if they have questions as well. But yeah,
OK, cool. Alright, sounds good.
I have two more questions on this.
So Paul, are you guys able to
meet with Brad to figure out what
clean up of this this epic and
moving the stories into their correct
statuses and assigning dates here?
I think it required some stuff with me
first and those guys to like understand
what that was going to be. So I think
we're we're just about there.
Um, so yeah, we can connect with the
mirror has been out for a couple of days
as well during this, so he didn't join
those conversations we just had. So there
he hasn't made any updates yet, but in
our next.
Um. I think
about the scrum name is for this, but in
our next session with Murad, we'll we'll
fix that. OK so Maracas off the last
couple of days. Yeah, he was he's been
sick for a few days. Ohk OK yeah, he
had said Wednesday, Thursday there
there's going to be like some sort of
realignment or. Refinement
review of yeah, he's been out
for both of those days. So
OK, but Michael is working, is
working on these modules now. So
keep in mind Andrew, that sort
of.
Mike and his counterparts who are
supporting Mike had just joined the
organization and they are coming up to
speed on how to do this stuff and they
needed some background information from
me on what exactly they were doing. So
they had taken a look at the work, came
back with a whole ton of questions about
how the pipeline works and. Than how they
need to do their code development and I
spent an hour with them this morning
actually, I spent half an hour with them
yesterday and then another hour this
morning going through all of that. So now
they're starting to progress forward. OK,
but we had to bring them up to speed,
right? And and honestly, I expect more of
that because their their new resources,
right? Like it's we airdropped people out
of the sky. Yeah, that's fair.
I thought the Katie had happened 2 weeks
ago, but now there was a general KT with
with another resource that we have, Dave
Lloyd. But once they started to dig into
the actual work, they came back with a
whole bunch more questions, which we
expect them and usually takes us like 3
months to bring someone up to speed.
Right. And these guys, you know, we,
we're crash coursing them in a couple of
weeks, right so.
But I there at the point now where
they're looking at the actual changes, So
and Paul, I, I gave them, I thought that
we had to finish the other core changes
before we went over to the lab module.
And if that's not the case, then then we
can redirect that and start focusing on
the lab stuff.
That sounds good. Can we have a ticket
for the QA that is happening of the
actual changes? Because I didn't see that
in the epic fall. No, the delivery, Well,
no, because the delivery team doesn't
work with this project. Yeah, alright,
fair enough. Yeah, right, right. So I
actually added the ticket because I
didn't think that we had made the PLT
module changes yet either. And so I
actually added a ticket to to to add
the core of the additional core
capabilities to the PLT module because I
hadn't seen the changes there, right, so.
We can dump that ticket if Brandon
already made those changes, but I didn't
think that we had gotten them into the
PLT module either. But they're exposed
to the, you know, the SD team model,
which means they're through the PLP
module, right? Yeah, yeah. Well, that
that is the PLP module. Yes, sorry. So if
that works already done and the PLC
module has feature parity with the core
module, then we can disregard that ticket
then. And and what we should be tracking
is the QA testing, right?
We can talk about that with Mira and
Paul. We just because this is The thing
is, is right, like Andrew needs to
understand where the status is and if
there's a bunch of two tickets and what
you're saying isn't being reflected in
Tierra, then how does he know?
So yeah, that was my concern or our
concern that was brought up last week and
we're out. Said that he would take care
of it.
So I think we'll probably just delayed
another week until we're back. Yeah, I
think he's I think he's, he was out the
last two days. I think he might be backed
today. I don't know if you saw him in the
scrum this morning, Paul, but I think he
might be back today. So we should have
this fixed in the next couple of days.
As far as like getting the
stories updated and stuff. OK, he's
back today is working.
OK, so maybe if we can follow up, I mean,
perhaps he doesn't do that. I don't know
when the meeting was scheduled for, but
he said. Wednesday, Thursday,
probably referring to backlog refinement,
which was yesterday. Ohh, OK.
OK. Yeah, If you guys can set up an ad
hoc meeting to do that would be great.
Otherwise, just let me know.
OK. And then Paul, there is just a
lingering action item now for the token
by times. You're going to take a little
bit to see what the parameters were.
Yeah, a little more competitive than I
thought. So I should just spin out myself
a story for it and actually track it
instead of forgetting about it four days
out of five? Sorry. I'll I'll
start the story.
OK.
OK, so few actions there.
Great. So let's move on to release
management. So Jeremy, the last update
was we have that call with Alex Cooper
Nov and he was supposed to reach out
to the gym, but did we ever hear
back? I think you yourself and like Rainy
were supposed to kind of continue to
please. I didn't hear back. Specifically
about that item, but I have
a larger update related to that.
So the one of the reasons why Alex was
hedging is because we're in the middle of
making a bunch of changes related to this
right now. Jim's
been heavily involved in that and we've
been, I've been working with Alex on some
up proposal for some pipeline changes
that are going to Megan.
So I we presented that
to Jim. He's on board.
I have a session with
where is it?
Umm. So the first step of that
is to rework our SOV rules. So
we have a meeting with Subodh and
some other folks.
Is it?I thought
it was tomorrow, but I think it might be
Monday.
Skype.
I don't know why I'm not seeing it, but
let me find it. Let me find the meeting
from Scott. Basically we're going to. We
are working through the.
Oh, there it is. It's actually next
Wednesday. Um, we are, we're working
through an uplift to the sod rules that
are going to allow us to.
Addressed this well, addressed the larger
issue behind this. Um, I, I don't know if
that also then allows us to make some
exceptions in the interim. That's the
open question, right? So I do need to
ping Alex on that. It's likely that he's
not going to allow that until we have an
answer on what target state is, which
we're hoping to get next week.
Um, so, um, unfortunately like
we can push, but I
don't know that.
I don't know that he's going to agree to
that until we understand where we're
going and get likes about and other folks
to buy into that. What what team is that?
Jeremy's that they could have team. It's
the pie is the the pipeline team.
I think they're, I don't know if they're
still called DSO. I don't even know what
DSO stands for, but I think that that's
their current acronym, Dev Secops, Dev
SEC OPS. OK, yeah.
Never made that correlation.
I think they're still Tiësto
Rajesh, but yeah, so, so,
so I'd probably just put
DSO. Yeah, so.
Yep.
The DSO pipeline is Trevor on this
call. See, there was none
on this call, James on this call.
And we obviously talked to prior about SD
rules and stuff and we had gone over that
with your team.
I don't know if you want any
participation in our in our working
sessions, unlike revising that SOD rule,
those SD rules based on our SDLC standard
and Wim standard. Either way, we're going
to end up coming back and presenting to
you, but if you want to participate, I'm
happy to invite someone.
I can decide whether I can get there or
not. And it's Donaldson,
Trevor or something else? Yeah. I mean,
Trevor's pretty. She's probably the most
familiar person from your team in this
cloud operating model. So yeah, Yeah, for
sure. Yeah.
Um, so yeah, unfortunately Jane and and
and you like it.
I, I've been trying to convince Alex just
give us an exception, but he's very leery
of that because he's got pressure from
Chris Tomlin and Subodh and stuff that
have gone to Jim and Megan saying, you
know, because there's been violations to
those existing SSD rules. They're
basically. Enforcing and validating the
BSOD rules that we have in place. And
the only way around that really is to
is to revise the SFD rules, right?
So he's very leery right now of, of
providing exceptions to that because of
the visibility this has at the moment.
OK. Uh, by the
way, I did open up that risk Jeremy
wants you to review, so I'm going to
e-mail you taking that to me and I'll
I'll make an update on it. OK.
And.
Yeah. Just sending that to you right now,
OK.
Tell you a lot of people out there
comment, OK?
Anything else around the pipeline
access?
Jeremy, should should we be going to down
that path of updating the roles or should
we just assume now that we need multiple
roles and we're we're going to use that
as an interim solution?
Should we be making the
overall capacity rule changes?
We are going to be making any of those
changes. It's not up to us to make those,
um. By we, I mean like this
particular audience, right, um.
My hope is that if we
get some initial agreement on an
allowed target state for the SD
rules, then we can implement some
quick changes that align to that
for this repository without getting into,
you know on in trouble.
Or we can get a latte that says, hey,
we're in flight to change these BSOD
rules and they're getting recertified. In
the interim, let's just make the update
to this repo because we know where this
path is and we've gotten nominal
agreement from Enterprise Protect and so
we can proceed, right? OK, I see. So it's
kind of like agreeing on a target.
Not necessarily implementing the target
state, but using that as a basis
to get the exception. Yes, OK, I
see.
OK, makes sense.
Umm. Alright, alright.
And I guess in terms of release
management and the question around how
will deployments be done, we do have
a a weekly series and there's just
a couple of action items.
For Wayne and Paul, Wayne
was going to provide.
Kind of the requirements around
documentation artifacts, etcetera to move
between environments as we promote
the configuration. And then I
think Paul you were you
had an action as well
to.
Figure out what is what improvements are
required based on what we have to. Yeah,
I think I, I just wanted to identify the
granular between identifying good
agreement kind of between Jane and the YM
team and they has team on like, hey, this
is how the things are going to work
operationally going forward. It's going
to be Tuesday, Thursday night
deployments. Or we're going to, who's
going to be submitting changes? Are we
going to get a bunch of standard changes
created? Are we going to? We did, we
talked about the secret generation, which
is identify all those things to make sure
that everybody agrees that the shared
process going forward is going to be XYZ,
as well as documenting that process. But
that's kind of separate. I'm going to
kind of help. Work through with the
delivery team on on some documentation of
the new process as opposed to to like
documentation of the process that we're
not going to use, but the process that
existed as it was in the past, so.
That's kind of where we
are, OK, And we have
some actions basically due by
our. On Monday.
OK.
Yeah. I mean, I don't think I have
anything else to to mention here other
than there's a conference where we're
documenting our discussion and actions
and just rotated discussion on Monday.
Anything else for release management?
Umm.
Thank you. Real quick, I just got
a e-mail earlier this week on it.
They're tracking the the, the sort of
new intake form and process. I've been
corrected as part of this effort. Yeah,
somewhere. Yeah, it's this, this one
here. Sorry. That's when you remember
the word that Karina is leading, right?
Yep. Yeah. So that that is pretty much
done. We're just on hold for now.
Although I think Karina was meeting with
you, Paul, too. Yeah, I saw a meeting
about it. I just didn't remember. It's
sort of like I didn't realize it was on
hold. It it's done
like it's it's not.
But we, we, we can't really deploy that
to prod until YM is ready, you know about
the transfer is completed and the team is
ready to start. So I
thought this was something just.
Anyway, that's the discussion. Yeah, I
didn't, I thought it was, I thought
it was kind of waiting on the
service now that do stuff. So yeah,
no, ServiceNow is is done. So OK,
let's see this conversation. Are we
duplicating work here?
Well, because you asked me to look at
requirements for future operation,
deployment process. Well, the service now
intakes done and the service now is kind
of ready and it's been put on hold
because we don't have the tool set to do
that. You've got, you've got
all the work that we've talked about
earlier in the discussion, right? You've
got all the work, that Terraform work
that has to be done, all that sod stuff
has to be straightened out, all the
that's like the technical deployment. So
we can't, we can't deploy anything until
that's in place as well. We have to get
a, get consensus on how. The two sets of
deployment processes are going to be
combined, right, Just like Paul was
saying, like we got to talk to Nahas
group to say, OK, we're going to do stuff
up to this point, then we're going to
hand this stuff over to you. And then we
have to figure out exactly how we're
going to move forward with, you know,
looking at which of the which of the
processes that are. Place at the moment
are actually, you know, which components
are we going to keep, which are being
removed, which are going to expand upon
like the entry ID. Team does deployments
during the day very directly in
production, Pink said. Team does
deployments Tuesdays and Thursday nights
be a change order with standard change
order. May all those types of things kind
of have to be rationalized. And that's to
me that's completely separate and
distinct for the most part from the
service now intake because that's we get
the service now intake and that that's
what kicks off those subsequent processes
that are in behind the scenes drug. So
those things have to be all that.
Work those discussions about how those
processes are going to play out that's
what we have to look at now and I
think we so we can talk and so the
the item you have from the previous story
right is is that I think last time we
were discussing some of this I don't
think the sort of governance and
tracking. Requirements are super clear.
So there may be some decisions that we're
making about OHH, can we send a secret to
only the person who's authorized on the,
you know, ServiceNow intake to receive
that secret or something? There's some
some things around that, which is like
what are the standards on how to do that?
What are the relevant behaviors so we can
make sure the procedure. Here's the
standards and I think that nobody sort of
had a clear beat on what are the
operative standards that we're trying to
align to. That is an open question. That
specific item is an open question that we
have because the development effort that
I was going to come back to you with Jane
as well. We can obviously target the TA
or delegate. Through the if
we're doing self-service automation and
we're sending a a starter secret to to a
person, especially since these are
technically non privileged, do we just
let them specify anybody to send it to?
Do we only send it to the DO and
delegate if we're doing that? What if
they're not there? Right? What if
they're, you know, usually the TA is.
Really disconnected, right? So how do we
know? Do we only send it to the
requester like the actual person who
submitted the change the the the
registration? Maybe we locked down to
that, right? We normally get the
requester or the TO to identify the
single person that we send it to. OK,
so in self-service. Be OK for a requester
to say send it here.
To this person, well.
We would have to look at that because we
don't want it to be somebody random. We
need it to be formal or formal
assignment, right? We need, you know,
you. I wouldn't want you to say all that,
you know, send whatever you need to to
Jane, right, Because you may not on the
app. I may not own the app. We need to
get. Kind of formalization in there.
Well, person, this is the thing with this
self-service, right is the trade off is
as we have to think about like these
types of wonky things, you know, if
they're putting in a ServiceNow request,
you can just specify it as a field right?
In the fact that the TA is approving
means it's OK. But in self-service
automation, obviously we don't we have
the TA O that. Approved for the opcode to
be leveraged but they're not approving
the individual flow right so that means
that we're locked down to either one of
three people that we know right we know
the requester so we know the person who's
doing the work who's who's who's actually
promoting the the the app registration
we. Executing, right, it's typically
going to be like one of the limb
developers that's authorized against that
app code, right? Or we know that a or
the delegate like those are the three
people that we know, right, but for
certain, right great. So then then do we
have to put something or stipulate
something in the approval that the.
They'll have to provide to say that he's
that person is OK with whoever is named
as a recipient of the secret so that
she knows that that's one of the pieces,
you know, but so it's kind of who
does approve that. What
the requester is actually asking for in
that, so, so who approves right, is
someone who's authorized by the WTO to
be an approver, right. So it would
be a developer lead that would that
would approve the PR and for the
release it would be someone who's
identified as a release. Specialist and
those that those roles have to be
approved by A to and the growth and the
releases are patent. Do you have to be
tied to a change which is well, obviously
that's absolutely true, but the change
would require the Tao to proof that
that's being done.
There may be a way for us to check to
see that um. You know if they
specify someone that they are in that
group of people who are authorized
against the app code, like they're in a
dev lead or a release specialist
position, right?That's a little
bit more advanced, but it may we may have
that capability to say, hey, if you've
been approved for a role against this
deployment from the TA O, then it's OK to
send the secret to you. Exactly. That's
definitely what we can we can state that
somewhere in some kind of like on a, you
know, a confluence site and agreement.
Something so that we cover our collective
when that, you know, for those cases,
yeah, it's going to be some funky coding
on our Paul that we'll have to look
at, but it's yeah. And it's amazing. How
stringent does that need to be? Where's
the kind of requirement or process on how
to handle that right? Can we be?More LAX
about it. Can we be more than other than
dev, right. Can we are there are there
whether this whether what's the standards
around that and how should we how should
we design that? Because there's lots of
options for that. But that's not the only
situation where there's a decision around
that. No, I don't. That's just one
example, right. One one of many examples.
Yeah, just like anything else.
Just like anything else for self-service,
if they can't meet the requirements for
self, we're trying to hit a 9010 or an
8020 rule here, right? If they can't meet
the 80% right, then they go through the
intake process, right, and they're not
eligible. Yeah, yeah. This thing that we
have to understand too is what we've run
into in the past. That self-service
usually ends up in a lot of crap
somewhere that somebody's going have to
weed through eventually they get
self-service means try, try, try again.
Yeah. Seeing the benefit, one of the
reasons why we wanted the benefit
pipeline, Jane, is that it's it's.
When they try, try, try again, it
destroys and redeploys, right? Yeah, it
puts the ownership on them to to
do that destroy and redeploy, right? And
so, yeah, we, we can talk about
that more, but there's, there's, there's
better options than, for example, us.
Having to go out and start
to clean up ourselves, right, Yeah.
Good. That's comforting, though, OK.
Good discussion. To
assign this to you like who's developed
developing those rules or those
standards. Well, that was, but that was
part of, and I guess we didn't, we
weren't super explicit about it, but that
was part of what the I think that what
we were talking about with Wayne is like
what are the operative standards around
many of the operations in this process.
Around the average deployment process
which includes both stuff that might be
applicable to self-serve and it's just
applicable to hey, we're doing this in
EDP, right. We're doing this even the
delivery teams are doing this deployment
at ADP, which is a different tool,
completely different tool set than what
they currently use. And are there any
processes that are kind of. Reactive to
helping fed does things or picked the
deployment process that we need to
confirm whether we're going to persist
like kind of that that release schedule
being done with distinct release people
versus our team. Like is that distinction
actually is there a standard that drove
that distinction or or and if there is
a standard?That distinction is that kind
of handled by the way the EDP structures
things that we don't need to do the
same kind of thing where the where the
where the we follow the same kind of
release pattern that thinks it does. I
think those are the standard. Those are
the questions that are governed by
should. Hopefully have links to
underlying reasons that they were done
and that we can use to reevaluate.
Whether the how the new process is
aligned to them?
Hopefully that makes sense. And that's a
very big bucket of work. And they give me
all the standards that make you do what
you do today because we don't know if we
have to do that. That would be heard on
our part too, but just.
We can just look at it as far as our
deployment process is great and we can
start there and say, OK, here's how the
deployment process works, Here's why we
have to do it this way. And then that
should hopefully inform the target
process as to what, how, what we have to
handle on it. And we can do that for me.
KFJC wait on my call anymore? Is
this going to be assigned to await?
Yeah, since he left, absolutely.
OK, that's good for leaving.
Just going to learn well I I would say it
already was assigned to wait it just.
Yeah, you missed a lot of that
discussion. At least he has the answer to
the first part, which is that who we have
this?
So thought that was speculation, right?
No. Was that not speculation? That seemed
like we were speculating that that might
be the requirements. Yes,
there's actually.
OK, sounds good.
Alright, get discussion. This
one's on hold.
OK. So let's move on
to the enterprise rollout, um,
token exchange tomorrow. I think
we're still waiting on VOD.
Yeah, it's the same. It's the same still
applies. They're looking at July, August
time frame. The meeting that was supposed
to happen hasn't been scheduled yet.
But I suspect there's, there's not a
whole lot to discuss, right. I mean,
there are already a customer of Pink that
so it's just need to be shifted over to
ENTRA and most of that token exchanges
needs to be done from the application
team side. So I don't know.
What needs to be discussed with the
vendor? But can we, can we nudge them
again tomorrow?Yeah, I'll,
I'll ping the tail, OK.
And then in terms of APIM, you
guys met and basically still no
candidates on that side, right?
Yeah, yeah. Socially, they weren't too
sure of what the requirements were for
token exchange. They introduced us to one
of the tales of.
I guess one of the Isengard apps that are
now using Entra for authentication. Ohh
alright, that's it. They they told us
that they have a fully fledged test API
and a client application in all three
environments and they would be able to
test this. Why are they redirecting us to
line of business people? That is not what
we discussed. And and it
isn't guard stuff isn't isn't guard
doesn't do I don't understand why
that's even applicable. Would be
appreciated like across we crossed some
wires here that we need to
unwind. Yeah, because I remember talking
to Marie about this MAHRI that
individual from AIM. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She originally stated that or thought
that it might, there might be a candidate
on their side. But when we dug into it a
little bit more, she kind of has more
said, kind of backpedaled on that. I
don't think she's the right person to
talk to. We should be talking to Paul and
Christian. Photoshoot and find out
if he's got any energy, knows of any
candidates for this. We have another call
with them. Actually, I think I have
another call with them later today. I
think we we do Jade and actually, yeah,
at 3:00. I'm going to hammer them on this
at 3:00. Yeah, I didn't let them know
they have a separate request there.
They're obviously standing up their API
validation. Functionality for NYPD, so
we're kind of giving them a
POC around that, but that actually,
Jeremy, this is another thing.
Well, no, if we ever expose it,
I guess exposing API's through a
self-service functionality and then
adding, making sure that there's a way
for them to opt in to APIM,
APIM. Automatic validation tool
connectivity into that it's kind of its
own separate thing. So maybe we're we're
not we're not allowing API onboarding
through self-service at the moment We
that's maybe maybe some future thing down
the road and I haven't wrapped my head
around how we do that yet, but we're
we're we're light years from that at this
point but. Actually, even if we do it the
the separate conversation with 18, sorry,
it's not really related. And I, yeah, but
I want to be careful. While I understand
that there are some interdependencies
between what Adam is doing and what we're
doing, I want to be very careful not to
derail what we're doing because of Adam.
But I did, I did. They didn't seem to be
interested in validating token exchange
themselves. So I did provision them for
access to one of the APIs or they you
seem to be able to encourage them to be
interested in. But I haven't set them up
with anything because I just needed, I
wanted to confirm on the call today
whether that's something that they're
that they themselves will test them and I
could. I'd like to something easily
that'll let them leverage it if they
fully understand the flow and are going
to actually run through it.
But but that's obviously not a client
application. But it might be better than
nothing. Ignore.
I totally agree.
Hear from Shishu too.
Jerry, could you drop that name in the
chat?
SHISHU space PAL.
That's the first
name. Last
name. They have a different last name.
That's what I yeah, Kumar.
She can go to the market.
OK.
Yeah, I don't think that's huge. I'm
always worried about misspelling people's
names, like that's why I ask.
Right.
Got it. She should
help Kumar.
Perfect.
OK, OK. Sounds good. Anything
else for token exchange?
We're working with that now. So it might
take 100% to you. The other question
you're being asked that would be
calculated. We're good, OK.
Jeremy, that was custom, custom claims
provider. You introduced us to your
developer a couple weeks ago, I think.
Yeah. How's that going? It's going well,
actually I just was on with them
for an hour at 11. We're just
finishing up. There was some. Houses with
deploying the infrastructure, but we're
just finishing up that now. Ash is
already working on some of the early
development for this as well. So far
we've got most of the components
deployed. I think the actual function
itself like the the infrastructure for
the function will be deployed either.
Later today or tomorrow and then we have
another working session on Monday to get
into some of the details and also pretty
staged some of the data. I
actually think some of that will be
based, some of that data staging will be
based on the session we have tomorrow at
10:30 where we decide on what some of
those attributes are, which is going to
help me define what data needs to be
staged. That's the meeting tomorrow,
right? Yep. OK. So I, I
think we're, we're on track, Um. The
the the work is progressing. I've got
2 folks actively working on this right
now. And umm, yeah,
Archie, technically a little bit. The
lady said this would be done like
not last Monday, but the Monday before.
What would be done? The deployment, the
SQL DB staging, infrastructure
deployments. Yeah, the inventory is
deployed for the SQL database. I don't
have the. At this stage, because we
haven't decided on the data yet, which is
one of the conversations for tomorrow, I
thought that we'd have the function
deployed before now, but there are some
challenges with deploying the function
and needed some other things that weren't
super clear. And we had some some
struggles with deploying the
infrastructure, but it's it's it'll be.
Will be done tomorrow. Yes, that is a
little bit delayed, but do I think that
it impacts the overall timeline as far as
the work that we're doing in Q3 now?
Still expecting completion
by tomorrow.
For infrastructure deployment yet, not
for like full development of the app
itself, yeah.
OK, um, and this hasn't
started yet, right? Local testing
with API?
Um, no, it has not. Well, Ash has been
working on pulling some stuff together,
but obviously needs some data for me,
like what attributes are we hooking into
and stuff? So they have some stuff
shelled out. So I guess I shouldn't say
that it hasn't started at all, but it's,
it hasn't proceeded very far. OK.
Just say it has begun, that's
fine. And then the network integration
approvals, I haven't gone back down
that road yet.
Sorry to ask, any ETA?
Um.
Not necessarily. There's too many things
that are on my plate nature. I understand
a lot of other moving parts on this
program, so.
I'd like to remember is 1 punted that
Jeremy and wanted to discuss with. It was
a Tony wasn't it?
Uh, yeah. And I've talked to Tony about
this. Uh, I have to get back with Tony. I
just, I just have it in cycles and
there's other stuff that's more pressing
at the moment, so. Um, so I
haven't got back to this yet. I was
waiting until I was giving it a couple
more weeks until we get.
Something out there in the Ng lab so
I can show him. Usually that helps the
conversation.
OK. Yeah, nothing to show on that kind of
makes it a moot point since the
discussion that. And
then the glossary is that been started?
Yeah, I've been clicking the data points
that glossary is. Um.
I have that in a subtask in my story,
Andrew and I, I think I started to
actually feed some, some information into
there. But I if I haven't updated the
story, I'll go and update it. But but
yes, I've been pulling in some of the
data. I haven't talked to Paul yet.
And I Paul, we do need to chat about
this. I just obviously last week was a
bit of a wash because of the on sites in
Toronto and then I was sick for a couple
of days the beginning of this week, but.
I've got a bunch of the data together.
Some of that will come out in the
conversation tomorrow, Andrew, that we
have. Actually that's kind of the crux of
the conversation tomorrow. But I've been
collecting some information so we can
talk in the conversation tomorrow, OK?
OK, sounds good uh OK to
move on to VI and the
found VI Yep OK, so last
update Jeremy, you guys are finished
the use cases now you're basically
filled up building out the test
cases Yep so.
I've made some progress with that. Um,
I've done like 9 or so test cases and
identified a few questions and stuff
already. There's a bunch more that need
to be created. I have a meeting scheduled
with Manish on Monday and we'll work to
get those finished and also try to answer
some of the questions I see. Mike
Flemings on the call. I've already given
Mike a heads up that we're going to be
coming with a couple of requests in Dev.
Uh, one of the things that we'll have to
sort out with Manish is what test
accounts we want to use. And then we'll
have to request some BDI's for those test
accounts and make sure that they have
Citrix storefront access against the
various endpoints that we need.
Once we finalize the test cases, Mike, I
plan to meet back with you and just talk
about what's actually possible in dev.
I'm guessing that not all of the testing
is possible in dev because we have like
public facing stuff that I assume is not
available in depth. So I
have to talk about if the test is
applicable, whether or not we could even
do that. And whether
or not we can even test in dev
if we do need to do that, right?
Yep. And then we'll have at least one,
I think we'll there'll be a conversation,
Mike, where we want to look at like
what you have published against like
you're deaf Citrix storefronts.
And we might be able to select an
app out of that that we could enforce
for multifactor, um. And if not,
we might ask you to publish like a web
URL for an app that we have, even if
it's something dumb like the Azure portal
or something like that. So that way we
can validate multifactor through that,
right? Yeah. I mean, basically anything
that's published in production, we can
just get the packaging team to deploy to
a dev. Server for you, so let's
go back home, OK?
All right. So we'll work through that and
then we'll set something up with
yourself, Mike or whoever you delegate
and we can just get make sure we have the
right infrastructure set up so that way
we can execute some of those tests
separately from that. I think that
there's a more fundamental conversation.
So Jonathan, if you're on, hopefully you
are.
This is Jonathan. OK, Jonathan here.
Sweet. OK, so my thoughts for this as I
started to get into the test cases where
let's just test what happens if we change
nothing in the existing VDI environment
and just start the MFA applications, what
happens, right. And so I start to scope
the test cases. From that and pretty
quickly ran into some questions about um.
For example, like what happens if someone
has Windows Hello for business, um. Only
and but does go to VDI and then needs
a prompt. Will that work? Will it prompt
them for Windows Phone for business
through the BDI somehow, right?
I assume no, right. And what happens if
they have authenticator and which is low
for business, which is just fall back to
authenticator just when there's low
actually isn't available on the DVD I
would assume yes, right. And so those are
kind of the things that we want to test.
And what I also ran into very quickly was
a lot of people are using secondary
accounts to get into VI. That are not set
up for multi factor, right. So can you
actually set up multi factor from the BDI
when prompted right or from Citrix
Storefront more specifically is what I
was thinking, right. Yeah. So I think
that there are some different use cases
for storefront versus like actual BD. I
think VDI is a little bit more
straightforward because you're on a VM.
And the VM should be able to get to,
um, Azure to register, except for the
vendor VDI, which will not have access to
the Internet, right? So we'll have to
talk about that. And that actually these
test cases are really good to iterate
through because it reminds me of things
like, hey, we're going to have to
actually make sure that all of our
vendor. The eyes are open to our security
registration portal because otherwise
they can't even register for multifactor.
Yeah. I mean, we're, we're gonna
quickly get into the you need
MFA to register for MFA. Yeah.
Yeah. So we need to look at that. So I, I
kind of wanted to go through the test
cases that I came up with with you. I can
invite you to that Monday afternoon
meeting if you want, with me. So we can
kind of dive into that a little bit.
Yeah, I'm doing a graduation on Monday,
so I'm off. I'm off. Never mind. OK, so
Monday won't work, but we'll, we'll,
we'll reconnect up to that. Because we're
going to talk about like how this impacts
from a design perspective, right? Like
there's things that we're going to have
to account for on this. But but what
I wanted to do, there's another, there
are other options that we can start to
dig into, right? Like Citrix does support
entry integration from a Citrix Workspace
perspective. And so one of the, the
conversations will be like if there's a
bunch of failures in these test cases, do
we test the entry integration in dev and
then look at what passes through there,
right? Like can we pass MFA through that
because of the interactive integration?
Does that help our test cases, etcetera?
And do we need to make a VDI
infrastructure change in order to support
MFA?With the underlying applications,
yeah, I think it's going to be it's going
to be all of the boundaries that give us
the trouble, right. So integrating with
intro will absolutely smooth these out,
right. The boundary goes away yeah. So my
my thought on this is that we test
against the existing environment first
with our use cases agree on what what
we're. What what we're going to see
from a test case perspective and prove
that those things are going to break and
then look to do the entry integration and
and see what that fixes. Yeah, that's
that's the I thought that's what we
discussed. I mean, we do the test cases,
we see what fails or. However, we
describe it expected behavior and see
where the gaps are and what solutions
could be.
Yep. OK, so we're, we're detailing those
out now. I'll, I'll, it's on the same
page, but I'll, I'll, I'll look to
connect with you early in the week and we
can. See if you
have any additional input to that. OK.
The Minish hopeful still plan to meet on
Monday. And we'll drag it out further.
Thanks, Sherry.
OK. All right. We have 7 more
minutes, so let's quickly go through if
I do 2 rollouts.
I think this one is interesting. I'm
starting to get a lot of questions
from all the retail people that we
engaged through that CPP 1 intake and
all of them are kind of asking
the same thing, like they they're looking
for exact, so scope, exact timelines, the
drivers. I, I've been mitigating those
conversations and the difference between
what they need to do versus what we're
doing and they're kind of two separate
things. They have a different mandate
that they need. If their application came
on board the MFA, they have funding
Andrew and it's on them to make those
corrections or enhancements or. Whatever
they have to do to get it ready to
bombard MFA, that's on them. I am going
to work with them. Once we have our road
map that we're talking tomorrow, we're
starting to have that conversation and
dates and we'll align there and we're
going to communicate those dates out to
them so they can know when they need to
have their work done.
Yeah. I see a note in here that like
you've reviewed the retail use cases that
Anthony Decosta has put together. I
haven't yet. It's still work in progress.
Yeah, you're going to say that that's
exactly my point, right? Like we have a 2
hour workshop with Anthony, I think
tomorrow morning, I know actually
tomorrow afternoon we're going to be kind
of detailing that. Further.
I can make a morning session and play,
make a surprise can I was in the morning,
didn't move it, I was in the afternoon.
It's 1:00 to 3:00 tomorrow.
Umm, I'm working with Anthony to kind of
to to document out those use cases.
Based on what we discussed in our
workshop last week, right, So it's not
just retail, it's the other photo use
cases as well. But obviously retail is a
heavy focus. That is
going to generate some questions for
retail based on some open things that
we'll find from there. And the point of
getting the retail engagement is that we
know who to talk to, to get those
questions answered, right? Yeah, I got
some names I'm going to talk to. Jan
Wilkinson is another person, Jeremy from
the retail case that potentially I could
take the floor. Have already and say hey
this is what I was getting from your
app teams what about the teller
onboarding experiences or something else
we're missing here yeah Jen Wilkinson
from WM where is there another Jan
Wilkinson No yeah, that's why I wasn't
sure why you were saying Jan because Jan
is from Wim yeah this is a. Different
Wilkinson then I guess this has to
do with teller onboarding she's business
not Liam no well so Jen does
work with Canadian retail when it comes
to centralized onboarding ohh yeah
because she has that matrix she also
handles it for the US that.
Sorry, Brian, you're breaking up.
Or Bruce Wayne.
I think there's two. I see there's two
looking teams. Interesting,
because you know you're all talking about
the. Breaking
up behind you Keep cutting out my
friend.
Um, either way, like I know they've been
really focused on US retail, but keep in
mind that we have to get some stuff from
Canadian retail too and they're pretty
different. OK, well, I want to because I,
Jonathan and I had a biweekly meeting
with. You know, we had a good discussion
on this. I had a good discussion with
them yesterday. They're they're ready to
go and they have volunteered a couple of
names as well. So I'm going to be setting
up a weekly just kind of status with
them. And then they also suggested
workshop as well. And they, they're
really keen and eager to talk about the
whole NFC reader part as well. Because
they've mentioned that their USB ports
are not accessible and then they have a,
you know, USDA I believe on the monitor.
But it's also not not very feasible to
use and plug it into the to the
monitor. So they probably require some
sort of NFC reader type device just for
clarity for yourself and for the. The
focus on this card just so that we're all
on the same page right at this point in
time, we understand enough about the
retail footprint that no matter which bio
use case we go with, we are either going
to have to deliver and install a dongle
or an NFC reader. There is no we're not
going to be asking retail to crawl under
their desk to plug in their keys. There
will be a a readily accessible dongle or
an NFC reader.
And so no matter what we're doing, there
is going to be a touch in the locations
to set this up. So when we're talking to
retail, when we're getting questions on
this, well we're understanding whether or
not we need on site support. The answer
is yes, absolutely. There's either going
to be a dongle to plug it into or they
will be a an NFC reader.
OK. So there's not
a lot of questions about that Andrew. And
I know that people have been going in
different directions on that. I I assure
you that it will be one of those two
things. OK, Yeah. So there there is a
good discussion overall. They're going to
assign a change lead from from the US,
sorry for Canadian retail side. Umm, they
do want to discuss their specific
use cases. They said that they
still have generic ideas there that
they're kind of concerned about and
they had questions around the shared
laptops spare pool scenario. They also
had questions around who's funding and
paying for the. Devices.
So it took various notes. I think we,
yeah, require workshops with them. And
but yeah, they, they know it's coming.
They're eager and ready to start working.
Yeah. And Mike, just keep in mind that
before you start going back to like Steve
Sparks and Jim on pricing for the Yubico
engagement, we also have to consider the
dongle, Leon. Like cost for field
services or the NFC reader, depending on
where we go. Yeah, perhaps.
For budget, but I can discuss that. We'll
bring that up and discuss with them
tomorrow because yeah, they're going to
be about 150 K for the on site services.
I got that estimate. We
don't know if we're going with dongles or
or NFC readers yet and the price will
vary depending on what we do with the
technicality depends on I said TBD, I'm
gonna need alright, you guys need to go
in the bank and attach something and they
gave me well for right now just give you
an estimate. You know it goes here and
they gave me 150 K for it.
As US and Canadian.
We're at time, but also Jeremy, just a
quick heads up, there is a decision also
made this week that we're going with the
OTP keys that's been documented.
Just as an FYI, who made that decision?
Mr. Generally, that's what we've been
saying is what we've been saying for a
while now, right until proven otherwise,
it's OTP. OK. So
that we can fully answer that, but we're
assuming that that's the case. Sure,
we're assuming, we're assuming that's the
case, right. You know, until we get many
months down the road and retail has done
testing and like that just doesn't work,
right. But we have we have to proceed on
that on that path until proven otherwise.
Right, because other otherwise, like, you
know, they were saying, OK, should we
stop? Should we pause? Like, no, we got
to, we got to move ahead. Yeah, I, I
think that there's a difference between
mainframe moving ahead with an assumption
and us making a program decision that
this is the only path.
Yeah, this, this is specific to
mainframe. Yes. I thought it was a
decision. No
decision is based on the design.
Right. And the design is based on the
requirements and the other things that we
pulled together, right?
Which we're certainly not out of job yet.
Now it will likely be OTP keys, don't get
me wrong. Right.
Again, we need to figure that out, right?
Like when we go to perfect concept this,
if we find that it's untenable, then
we'll be changing course, right?
But I think that's what that's what you
intended, right, Jonathan? Well, George,
yeah, absolutely. And what we know at the
moment, OP should, should address the
requirements. If we find if we find
outliers to that, then we move on those
outliers. But for the most part 80209010,
whatever we want to call it. Should
be able TP yeah yeah. And if we're not
we're not going to do the other it's just
this is this is how we can proceed at
the moment yeah like if the choice was OK
well let's let's pause mainframe for you
know six months until we're 100% sure
that doesn't make any sense right so
let's let's. Proceed in the assumption
that it is OTP, right? That's the
solution that does meet both mainframe
and retail and then we'll you know,
ultimately we'll see how it plays out,
OK. And changes very quickly. The
Epico MSA is going well.
Want to say it's going OK?
OK, sounds good. Alright, we're overtime.
Thank you, team. Appreciate it. And yeah,
we'll, we'll connect next week. Thank you
so much. Bye now.
And all that stuff down, it's down that
far, right, but.
Basically.
OK.